Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4192
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files
1976-1993
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Harper, Shirley
/4192
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8036614
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 24, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Harper, Shirley F.; Martin P. Catherwood Library; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Librarian's Office.
8036614
- Bldg Project Files - S. Harper 1962-1993 (Box 1)
  - Photographs of the Ives Building (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    32 photographs
  - Consultants, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    June 1991
  - Garrison Lull, Inc., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    June 22 and 23 1993
  - Garrison/Lull Inc., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    February 1993
  - Garrison/Lull Inc., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    May 1992
  - Garrison/Lull Inc., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    January 1992
  - Garrison/Lull Environmental Considerations, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    March 1991
  - Conservation Environment Consultation and Suggested Program Prepared for the Martin P. Catherwood Library by Garrison/Lull, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    December 1990
  - Architectural Consultations, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Delaney Operable Windows, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    September 1988
  - Facilities Program for Expansion and Renovation, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    August 12 1987
  - Summary of Acquisitions, 1982-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - State University Construction Fund Budget Estimate, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    February 26 1987
  - Delaney Documents, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    April 28 1987
  - Palleson Memorandum, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    April 3 1987
  - Palleson Miscellaneous Notes (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Letter from Nathan Fawcett to Lew Roscoe, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Documents of the Planning Group, ILR Division Directors and RPL Committee, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    February 23 1987
  - Documents on the Catherwood Library Use and Contents, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Documents on the Use of Catherwood Library, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Summer 1986
  - Spreadsheets for the Catherwood Library, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    July 1986
  - Delaney Project, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Fall 1984
  - Facilities Program Plan for the Expansion and Renovation of the Martin P Catherwood Library, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    May 1 1983
  - Miscellaneous Documents, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Facilities Program Plan for Expansion and Renovation of the Martin P Catherwood Library, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    April 1983
  - Building Documents from 1962 Files, 1956-1966 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Plans for the Expansion and Renovation of Mann Library, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Documents on the Expansion and Renovation of Mann Library, 1953-1983 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Bldg Project Files - S. Harper 1989-1993 (Box 2)
  - Notes on History of Martin P Catherwood Library Space Plans, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Project and the State Government, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Senator Kenneth P LaValle, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    October 28 1987
  - Newspaper Clipping for Expansion Project, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Legislation and Division of the Budget Visits, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Videotape on Library Space (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Library Advisory Committee Documents, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Projected Space Requirement Diagrams (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of a library, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Contains 4 photographs
  - M. C. Nesheim Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - State University Construction Fund Costing, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence and Documents Regarding the Library Project, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Comparison of the Olin and Law Library, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Campus Comparison Collections, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    January 1989
  - Appendix B Detailed Program, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Construction Sequence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Justifications for the Expansion Plan, 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Diagrams and Drawings for Library, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - General Information and Traffic Flow (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Existing Space By Function (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Collection and Shelving, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Contains 2 photographs
  - SUNY Cost Estimate, 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Current Space Allocation (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Collection Growth Mason Report Cornell University Library Campus Calculations, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Staffing Summary (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Articles on Library Construction, 1984-1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Square Feet Ratios and Cost of Academic Libraries, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Justified Construction Cost, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Visitors to the Library, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Traffic and Circulation, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Library Use Data, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Standards and Criteria, 1974-1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - SUNY, Cornell and Back Conversions (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Space Requirements and Conservation, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Space Summaries and Requirements, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Security Gate, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Security, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    September 1992. Restricted
  - Construction and Humidity Standards for Archives, 1984-1989 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Cornell, Design, Site and Construction Standards, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Site Development Criteria, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 120 Expansion Layouts (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 120 Expansion Layouts (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Displacement Costs, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Storage Questions, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Storage, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Shelving 154-155, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Storage and Displacement, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- HR files 1949-1990 (Box 3)
  - Personnel, Application for Nonprofessional Position, 1955-1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Restricted
  - Personnel, Applications for Professional Positions, 1956-1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1990 Classifications Review Part 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1990 Classifications Review Part 2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Personnel, Exempt Accrual Balances, 1983-1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Personnel, Exempt Job Descriptions and Responsibilities, 1973-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Personnel, Exempt Job Descriptions and Responsibilities, 1949-1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Personnel, General, 1958-1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Personnel, Employee Benefits, 1979-1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Human Resources, General, 1976-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Job Restructuring, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Personnel, Job Descriptions, Audiovisual Department, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Personnel, Nonexempt Job Descriptions and Responsibilities, 1979-1989 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Personnel, Nonexempt Job Descriptions and Responsibilities, 1964-1978 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Library Staff Changes, Offer Better Moving Allowance, 1973-1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Personnel, Organizational Charts and Job Classifications, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Personnel Records, Part Time and Temporary, 1977-1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Reclassification Requests, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Catherwood Library Staffing Changes, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Personnel, Student Employment Info Publications, 1985-1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Personnel Student Employee Job Classifications and Wage Scale System, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Personnel Student Employment, 1970-1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Personnel Student Employment, 1981-1988 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Personnel, Student Job Descriptions and Responsibilities, 1981-1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Personnel Student Job Requisition Forms and Lists, 1985-1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Personnel Wage Rates Student and Part-time, 1970-1989 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- CIT & Computers 1980-1992 (Box 4)
  - CIT, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - CIT Statements for 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - CIT Statements for 1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - CIT Statements for 1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - CIT Statements for 1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Computer Account for Library Acquisitions List, 1982-1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Computer Center, Bernoulli, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - CIT Documents, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Computer Equipment Service Warrantees, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Computers, Online Costs, 1976-1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Computers, Online Information Services, 1978-1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Computer Repair and Component Installation, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Computer Services Accounts, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    July 1980 - July 1982
  - Computer Services Accounts, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    1983/1984 and 1984/1985
  - Computer Services Statements, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    1985/1986 and 1986/1987
  - Computer Services Statements, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    1987/1988 - 1989/1990
  - Computer Services Statements, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)